What would I do without your smart mouth?
Drawin' me in and you kicking me out
God, my head spinning
No kidding, I can't pin you down
What's goin' on and that beautiful mind?
I'm your magical mystery right
And I'm so busy, don't know what hit me
But I'll be all right, my hands are burned
A cause of hers and all your edges
Are your perfect imperfections
Give me all, I'll give my end and my beginning
Even when I lose, I'm winning
Cause I give you all
He times do I have to tell you
Even when you crying, you're beautiful to her
The world is unfore, you're my muse
My worst distraction, my rhythm and blues
I can't stop singing, it's bringing in
My rhythm, furs and all, even on confessions
Give me all, I'll give you all, I'll give you all